careercruising.com 2012-11-22

# Career Cruising

  * Terms of Use
  * Portfolio End User Agreement
  * Site Administrator Agreement
  * Privacy Policy
  * Copyright Notice

Career Cruising respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. The information you provide is used to enhance your experience on our website, and to serve you efficiently. We will never sell or rent your personal information to any third party. This privacy statement explains the ways we collect and use information, and the ways we protect your privacy.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect personal registration and authentication information from users of our website. This data may include names, addresses, and email addresses. This information is used to create and maintain your subscription and to provide the services you request. By registering for our service you consent to this collection and use of your information.

It is possible we may be required to disclose personal information in order to comply with a law or government regulation. Otherwise, we will not disclose your personal information without your consent.

All of our employees and agents who have access to personal or confidential information during the course of their work duties are bound to maintain confidentiality.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

Non-personal information is data that is not associated with a specific personal identity. Career Cruising uses IP addresses, cookies, and usernames and passwords to collect general, non-personal information about site usage. This data includes the number of visitors that log onto our site, and the pages they access. The information collected is used to analyze usage trends and make improvements to the site.

**Accessing Your Personal Information and Opting Out**

You have the right to review, correct, or withdraw any personal data you have provided to Career Cruising.

  * **Administrators**

Career Cruising sends monthly newsletters to administrators via email. If you would like to opt out of this service, please contact us at 1-800-965-8541 or email us at [privacy@careercruising.com](mailto:privacy@careercruising.com). You can also change your personal information by contacting us at the above number or email address. If you are no longer an administrator and would like to delete your personal information, please contact us.

  * **Portfolio Users**

If you have set up a portfolio within Career Cruising, you can log into your portfolio and change your personal information online.

**Links to Third-Party Websites**

Career Cruising provides links to other websites for your information. If you access those links, you will leave the Career Cruising website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all third-party sites carefully before submitting your personal information. Any personal data you choose to give to unrelated websites is not covered by this privacy policy.

**Contact Information**

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact our Privacy Officer at [privacy@careercruising.com](mailto:privacy@careercruising.com).
